Products

Customers

Resources

Products

Free ToolsPremium ToolsData & Services

Tools

Rankings

[Data-as-a-Service

Power your business with digital insights at scaleLearn more](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/daas/)[Advisory Services

Get data driven answers to your business’s most strategic questionsRead more](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/advisory-services/)[Data Licensing

Data LicensingLearn More](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/oem-data/)

Customers

Customers

[Discover the brands shaping ecommerce

From athleisure to quiet luxury, discover which brands are shaping 2024 and the consumer trends and strategies driving their success.Download now](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/research/market-research/state-of-ecommerce/)

Resources

Resources

Education

Company

[Discover the brands shaping ecommerce

From athleisure to quiet luxury, discover which brands are shaping 2024 and the consumer trends and strategies driving their success.Download now](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/research/market-research/state-of-ecommerce/)

Search

Popular:

[

google.com](https://www.similarweb.com/website/google.com/)

[

facebook.com](https://www.similarweb.com/website/facebook.com/)

[

twitter.com](https://www.similarweb.com/website/twitter.com/)

[Home](https://www.similarweb.com/)Privacy Policy (website)

Privacy Policy (website)
========================

**Last Amended: June 20, 2024**

Similarweb Ltd., together with its group companies listed below (“**Similarweb**,” “**we**,” “**our**,” or “**us**”) provides innovative market intelligence services to our customers and users (“**you**”). We provide this policy (“**Privacy Policy**”) to make you aware of how we collect and use information pertaining to your use of similarweb.com (our “**Website**”) as well as the services that you access through the Website (our “**Services**”). We do not use information collected from users through their use of this website to power our analytics services. We also explain in this Privacy Policy certain rights that you have in respect of your Personal Information (as defined herein). Note that this Privacy Policy does not govern the Similarweb mobile app or browser extension.     

**Quick Reference Guide**

This Privacy Policy provides you with information about:

1. Personal Information We Collect
2. How We Use Personal Information
3. How We Share Personal Information
4. Cookies and Third Party Services
5. Analytics
6. The Legal Basis for Using Your Personal Information
7. Transfers of Personal Information
8. How We Protect and Store Your Personal Information
9. Your Information Collection Choices
10. Rights for EU and UK Residents
11. Additional Privacy Information for California Residents
12. Use by Children
13. Changes to this Policy
14. How to Contact Us

Similarweb is the controller of your Personal Information, under European Union (EU) and UK data protection laws. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, Similarweb’s group companies include Similarweb Ltd. (an Israeli company), Similarweb Inc. (a Delaware company), Similarweb UK Ltd. (an English limited company), Similarweb France SAS (a French company) Similarweb KK Japan (a Japanese company), Similarweb Australia Pty Ltd. (an Australian company), Similarweb Germany GmbH (a German company), and Similarweb SG Pte Ltd. (a Singapore company).

To read our Terms of Service, visit [https://www.similarweb.com/corp/legal/terms/](https://www.similarweb.com/corp/legal/terms/).

Similarweb’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

Similarweb’s use and transfer of information received from Google APIs to any other app will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

1. **Personal Information We Collect**

We collect information that identifies, describes, or is reasonably capable of being associated with you (“**Personal Information**”) when you create an account with us, use our Website or Services, or otherwise communicate with us.

**Personal Information We Collect Directly From You**

We may collect Personal Information from you if you choose to create a Similarweb account or use our Website or Services. The Personal Information we collect from you depends on how you interact with our Services, but generally includes the following:      

* * **Contact Information.** We may collect your name, email, work, or home address, and phone number when you set up an account with us. 
    * **Communications Information.** When you email, call, use any of our website enquiry form, or otherwise communicate with us and with members of our team, we may collect and maintain a record of your communications and our responses. We also maintain records of communications and information on our social media channels and information you provide to us related to any customer support requests.
    * **Employment Information.** We may collect your job title and employer when you set up an account with us. 
    * **Financial Information.** We use third party payment processors when you purchase a subscription for our Services, in order to process your payments for the subscription.

**Personal Information We Collect Automatically**

Like most website operators, we also may collect web server log information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available including: 

* Browser type;
* Language preference;
* Date and time of each visitor request;
* Referring URL;     
* Internet Protocol (IP) addresses;
* Operating System;     
* Device ID; and
* Advertising ID. 

This Information is collected for analytical purposes on a de-identified basis and cannot be used on its own to identify visitors to our Website. Our purpose in collecting this information is to better understand how our visitors use the Website in order to improve the Website and our Services.     

Some of this information will be collected using cookies and other tracking technologies. For more information on how we use tracking technologies on our Website, see the “Cookies and Third-Party Services” section below.

2. **How We Use Personal Information** 

Similarweb may use Personal Information for the purposes set out below: 

* **Operating Services and Providing Related Support.** To provide and operate our Services, communicate with you about your use of the Services, verify user eligibility to access restricted areas of our Website, provide troubleshooting and technical support, respond to your inquiries, fulfill your orders and requests, process your payments and claims, communicate with you about the Services, and for similar service and support purposes. 
* **Analytics and Improvement.** To better understand how users access and use the Services, and for other research and analytical purposes, such as to evaluate and improve our Services and business operations, to develop services and features, and for internal quality control and training purposes. 
* **Customization and Personalization.** To tailor content we may send or display on the Services, including to offer location customization and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences.
* **Marketing and Advertising.** For marketing and advertising purposes. For example, to send you information about our Services, such as offers, promotions, newsletters, and other marketing content, as well as any other information that you sign up to receive. This will be done where we have an appropriate legal basis and to the extent required by applicable law, we may obtain your consent for such marketing. We also may use certain information we collect to manage and improve our advertising campaigns so that we can better reach people with relevant content.  You can unsubscribe from receiving marketing messages by clicking on the unsubscribe button located in any of the messages you receive, or by contacting us at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com).
* **Security and Protection of Rights.** To protect the Services and our business operations; to protect our rights or those of our stakeholders; to prevent and detect fraud, unauthorized activities and access, and other misuse; conduct risk and security control and monitoring; where we believe necessary, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety or legal rights of any person or third party, or violations of our Terms of Service. To maintain our facilities and infrastructure and undertake quality and safety assurance measures.
* **Compliance and Legal Process.** To comply with the law and our legal obligations and to respond to legal process and related to legal proceedings. 
* **Business Transfers.** To consider and implement mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, and other business transactions, and, where necessary, to administer general business, accounting, recordkeeping, and legal functions. 

3. **How We Share Personal Information**

We share your Personal Information in the manner and for the purposes described below:

* **Vendors and Service Providers.** We may disclose Personal Information we collect to our service providers, processors, and vendors who perform functions on our behalf to allow us to provide the Services. These include IT service providers who help manage our IT and back-office systems.
* **Affiliates and Subsidiaries.** We may disclose Personal Information we collect to our affiliates or subsidiaries, who will use and disclose this information in accordance with the principles of this Privacy Policy.  
* **Third Party Platforms and Networks.** We may disclose or make available Personal Information to third parties in support of our marketing, advertising, and campaign management. 
* **Business Partners**. We may disclose Personal Information in relation to business transfers, when implementing mergers, acquisitions, or asset transfers. 
* **Government Entities.** We may also disclose Personal Information to regulators, government entities, and law enforcement when required by law or legal process. 

4. **Cookies And Third-Party Services**

**Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixels, and Other Technologies**

Our Website uses monitoring and tracking technologies including cookies and pixel tags. 

* **Cookies.** A cookie is a piece of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website using that browser. When you access our Website, we place cookies on your computer. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Sites, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities on our Sites. There are two types of cookies: session and persistent cookies.
    * **Session Cookies.** Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your device when you close your browser or turn off your device. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged in. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity after you have logged in, as you move through the website.
    * **Persistent Cookies**. Persistent cookies remain on your device after you have closed your browser or turned off your device. For removing cookies and other technologies used on our Website, please refer to the “Cookie Options” sub-section below.
* **Pixel tags**. Pixel tags (sometime called web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. While cookies are stored locally on your device, pixel tags are embedded invisibly within web pages and online content. We may use these, in connection with our Services to, among other things, track the activities of users, help us manage content and compile usage statistics. We may also use these in HTML e-mails we send, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded. 

**Third-Party Websites and Services**

Our Services may recommend third-party websites which we determine may be of interest to you (“**Third-Party Sites**”). Additionally, there may be links on our Website to third-party websites and services (“**Third-Party Services**”). We do not have control over such Third-Party Sites or Third-Party Services and are not responsible for their privacy practices or policies. We therefore recommend that you review the privacy policies of these Third-Party Sites and Third-Party Services before providing them with your Personal Information. For more information about the Third-Party Services to which links are included in our Website, please contact us at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com).

6. **The Legal Basis for Using Your Personal Information**

We will only collect, use, and share your Personal Information where we are satisfied that we have an appropriate legal basis to do this. This may be because:

* You have provided your consent to us using the Personal Information (e.g., where you provide us with marketing consents or opt-in to optional additional services or functionality);
* Our use of your Personal Information is necessary to perform a contract or take steps to enter into a contract with you (e.g., providing you with our Services, creating your user account);
* Our use of your Personal Information is in our legitimate interest as a commercial organization, subject to your interests and fundamental rights. In these cases, we will look after your information at all times in a way that is proportionate and respects your privacy rights and you have a right to object to processing as explained in the “Rights of EU and UK Residents” section below. Some of our legitimate interests include conducting analysis to better understand our Website visitors and to deliver content that will be relevant to our users;
* Our use of your Personal Information is necessary to comply with a relevant legal or regulatory obligation that we have (e.g., the disclosure of information to law enforcement or tax authorities).

If you would like to find out more about the legal basis for which we process Personal Information, please contact us at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com).

7. **Transfers of Personal Information**

Please be aware that some of the recipients of your Personal Information may be outside your country of residence from which the information was collected, including the United States, where our servers are located, and our central database is operated. This means that your Personal Information may be subject to a different standard of data protection than that available in your country of residence. Similarweb will take appropriate steps to ensure that transfers of Personal Information are in accordance with applicable laws and carefully managed to protect your privacy rights and interests. To this end:

* We ensure transfers within Similarweb will be covered by an agreement entered into by members of Similarweb (an intra-group agreement) which contractually obliges each member to ensure that Personal Information receives an adequate and consistent level of protection wherever it is transferred within Similarweb.
* Where we transfer your Personal Information outside Similarweb or to third parties who help provide our services, we obtain contractual commitments from them to protect your Personal Information. Some of these assurances are well recognized mechanisms for the protection of Personal Information transferred from within the EU or the UK to the United States or other countries. This may include the EU standard contractual clauses or the UK international data transfer agreement.
* Where we receive requests for information from law enforcement or regulators, we carefully validate these requests before any Personal Information is disclosed.

Subject to applicable laws, you have a right to contact us (at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com)) for more information about the safeguards we have put in place to ensure the adequate protection of your Personal Information when it is transferred as mentioned above. See the “Your Information Collection Choices” section below for more details. For information about your rights as a CA resident, please refer to the “Additional Privacy Information for California Residents” section below.

8. **How We Protect and Store Your Personal Information**

**Security**

We have implemented and maintain appropriate technical and organizational security measures, policies and procedures designed to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure or access to Personal Information. As the security of information depends in part on the security of the computer you use to communicate with us and the security you use to protect your user IDs and passwords, please take appropriate measures to protect this information.

**Retention of Your Personal Information**

We will store your Personal Information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, as explained in this Privacy Policy. In some circumstances we may store your Personal Information for longer periods of time, for instance where we are permitted or required to do so in accordance with legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements.

In specific circumstances we may store your Personal Information for longer periods of time so that we have an accurate record of your dealings with us in the event of any complaints or challenges, or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation relating to your Personal Information or dealings.

9. **Your Information Collection Choices**

You may revise your Personal Information by logging in and editing your account details. You also have the right to ask Similarweb to amend any Personal Information it holds about you if it is inaccurate or misleading by emailing our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@similarweb.com](mailto:dpo@similarweb.com) or [privacy@similarweb.com](mailto:privacy@similarweb.com).

You can ask us to stop sending email marketing, by following the ‘unsubscribe’ link you will find on all the email marketing messages we send you. Alternatively, you can contact us at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com). Please specify whether you would like us to stop all forms of marketing or just a particular type (e.g., email).

If you wish to prevent cookies or third-party advertisers from tracking your activity on our Website or visits across multiple websites, there are tools you can use to disable cookies and opt out of interest-based advertising. Using the resources below does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Website, Services, or on other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Your opt-out may not be effective if your browser is configured to reject cookies.

* **Browser Solutions.** You can decide if and how your computer will accept cookies by configuring the preferences option within your web browser, using the instructions provided in your browser. If you choose to decline cookies, however, some of the functionality of this Website might be impaired. For more information about how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
* **Industry Solutions.** Notwithstanding the above, visitors to our Website may follow the steps provided by initiatives that educate users on how to set tracking preferences for most online advertising tools, such as the Network Advertising Initiative ([https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/](https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/)) and the Digital Advertising Alliance ([https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/](https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/)).

In order to disable some cookies or otherwise adjust your cookie preferences, please adjust the settings on your browser. Please note that if you disable certain cookies on your browser, some parts of our Services may not fully work or may otherwise be limited or affected. If you use a new computer, upgrade, or change web browsers or take any action which results in the deletion of the “opt out” cookie, you will need to perform this opt-out process again upon any such change. You can also adjust your cookie settings or choose to reject certain types of cookies by clicking on the “Manage Cookies” button on the footer of our Website. You can change your cookie preferences at any time by visiting the cookie preference center via this “Manage Cookies” button.

We recommend you routinely review the privacy policies and preference settings that are available to you on any social media platforms you use, as well as your preferences within your Similarweb account.

10. **Rights for EU and UK Residents**

The following rights, which may be subject to certain exemptions, apply to EU and UK users:

* You have a right to access information held about you. Your right of access can normally be exercised free of charge; however, we reserve the right to charge an appropriate administrative fee where permitted by applicable law.
* You have a right to request that we rectify inaccurate Personal Information, and we encourage you to regularly update your account information. We may seek to verify the accuracy of the Personal Information before rectifying it.
* You can also request that we erase your Personal Information in limited circumstances e.g., where it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected, or you have withdrawn your consent (if the processing was based on consent) or following the successful right to object, or if the Personal Information was processed unlawfully. 
* You have a right to restrict the processing of your Personal Information, for example in case we no longer need your Personal Information for the initial purposes for which it was collected but it is required by you for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
* You have a right to object to processing which has our legitimate interests as its lawful basis. We will no longer process your Personal Information upon your request, unless we have compelling legitimate grounds for the continuation of the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. You may also object to our use of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes. See the “Your Information Collection Choices” section for how to unsubscribe, manage your marketing preferences and opt out of cookies.
* You have a right to obtain a portable copy of Personal Information which is processed on the basis of your consent, or which is necessary for the performance of a contract between us. You have a right to have such portable copy of Personal Information transferred to another data controller in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.
* You also have a right to request details of the basis on which your Personal Information is transferred outside the EEA or the UK but you acknowledge that data transfer agreements may need to be partially redacted for reasons of commercial confidentiality.
* You have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority if you have concerns about how we are processing your Personal Information. We ask that you please attempt to resolve any issues with us first, although you have a right to contact your supervisory authority at any time. You can find information on the relevant EU data protection authorities [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en#member-at) and the UK Information Commissioner’s Office [here](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/contact-us-public/). 

We may collect additional information to confirm your identity and for security purposes, before disclosing the Personal Information requested to you. We reserve the right to charge a fee where permitted by law, for instance if your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive.

You can exercise your rights by contacting us at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com). Subject to legal and other permissible considerations, we will make every reasonable effort to honor your request promptly or inform you if we require further information in order to fulfill your request.

We may not always be able to fully address your request, for example, if it would impact the duty of confidentiality we owe to others, or if we are legally entitled to deal with the request in a different way.

11. **Additional Privacy Information for California Residents**

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (“**CCPA**”), California residents have the right to receive certain disclosures regarding our information practices related to “Personal Information,” as defined under the CCPA. To the extent you are a resident of California and we collect Personal Information from you subject to CCPA, the following applies. 

This section does not apply to publicly available data, deidentified data, or aggregate data as defined by the CCPA, or to Personal Information we collect and process about Similarweb employees, personnel, and job applicants.

**CCPA Right to Know Disclosure**

While our processing of Personal Information varies based upon our relationship and interactions with you, the list below identifies the categories of Personal Information we have disclosed to third parties and which third parties we disclosed it to (as defined under CCPA) for a business or commercial purpose in the prior 12 months (from the Last Amended date at the top of this Privacy Policy):

* **Identifiers**
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries.  
    * Regulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order).
* **Internet and Electronic Network Activity Information**
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries.  
    * Advertising networks.
    * Regulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order).
* **Customer Records**
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries.  
    * Regulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order).
* **Purchase History and Tendencies**
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries.  
    * Regulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order).
* **Audio, Video, and other Electronic Data**
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries.  
    * Regulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order).

**“Sales” and “Sharing” under CCPA**

CCPA defines a “sale” as disclosing or making Personal Information available to a third party in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration. CCPA also defines “sharing” as disclosing or making available Personal Information to a third party for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising. 

While we do not disclose Personal Information to third parties in exchange for monetary compensation, we may “sell” or “share” (as defined by the CCPA) Personal Information, such as identifiers and internet and electronic network activity information to third-party ad networks. We do so in order to improve and evaluate our advertising campaigns and better reach customers and prospective customers with more relevant ads and content. 

We do not sell or share sensitive Personal Information, nor do we sell or share any Personal Information about individuals who we know are under sixteen (16) years old. We do not provide your Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you may have the following rights to your Personal Information: 

* **Request Access:** With respect to the Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months, you have the right to request from us (up to twice per year and subject to certain exemptions): (i) categories of Personal Information about you we have collected; (ii) the sources from which we have collected that Personal Information; (iii) our business or commercial purposes for collecting, selling, or disclosing that Personal Information; (iv) the categories of third parties to whom we have disclosed that Personal Information; and (v) a copy of the specific pieces of your Personal Information we have collected.
* **Request to Correct:** You have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information.
* **Request to Delete:** Subject to certain conditions and exceptions, you may have the right to request deletion of Personal Information that we have collected about you. 
* **Request to Opt-Out of Sale/Sharing:** You may have the right to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your Personal Information. To opt out of the sharing or sale of Personal Information collected through advertising cookies, please click on the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” link on the bottom of the Website homepage or visit the Manage Cookies in the footer of our Website. Please note that submitting an opt out request will only opt you out of disclosures that are considered “sales” or “sharing” under the CCPA, but it will not opt out of other disclosures, such as to our service providers. 
    * You may also opt-out of “sales” and “sharing” of your Personal Information through the use of an opt-out preference signal. If our website detects that your browser or device is transmitting an opt-out preference signal, such as the “global privacy control” or “GPC” signal, we will opt that browser or device out of cookies on our website that result in a “sale” or “sharing” of your Personal Information. Please note, if you come to our website from a different device or a different browser on the same device, you will need to opt out, or use an opt-out preference signal, for that browser and/or device as well.
* **Non-Discrimination:** We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of the rights described in this section.
* **Authorized Agent:** You may designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. To do so, you must provide us with written permission to allow the authorized agent to act on your behalf.

You can exercise the rights described above by:

(a) Contacting us at +972-3-5447782  
(b) Emailing us at [dpo@similarweb.com](mailto:dpo@similarweb.com) or [privacy@similarweb.com](mailto:privacy@similarweb.com) 

When you submit your request, we will take steps to attempt to verify your identity. We will seek to match the information in your request to the Personal Information we maintain about you. As part of our verification process, we may ask you to submit additional information, use identity verification services to assist us, or if you have created an account on our website or mobile app, we may ask you to sign into your account as part of our identity verification process. Please understand that, depending on the type of request you submit, to protect the privacy and security of your Personal Information, we will only complete your request where we are satisfied that we have verified your identity to an appropriate degree of certainty. We will l make every reasonable effort to respond to you within 45 days after we receive a verified request. If we are unable to meet this timescale, we will respond as soon as possible over the next 45-day period.

12. **Use By Children**

We do not offer our Services for use by children. If you are a minor, you may not use the Services or provide any information to the Website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children.

13. **Changes to this Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. We recommend checking back periodically for the latest version of the Privacy Policy, as indicated in the “Last Amended” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. We will not make material changes to how we use Personal Information without providing notice.     

14. **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to exercise your privacy rights, please feel free to contact us by email at [legal@similarweb.com](mailto:legal@similarweb.com) or dpo@similarweb.com.

[

](https://www.similarweb.com/en/)

Follow us on:

* [

    ](https://www.facebook.com/Similarweb)
* [

    ](https://x.com/Similarweb)
* [

    ](https://www.linkedin.com/company/similarweb)
* [

    ](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCVCI01HR6iB4AA4ChW08cvQ)
* [

    ](https://www.instagram.com/similarwebinsights/)
* [

    ](https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/dP9RRhIGCvDpdFh8hCKuww)

* Rankings

    Free Tools

* Solutions

    Data

* Resources

* About us

Our Offices See all Similarweb offices

* Givatayim, Israel

* Burlington, US

* New York, US

* Sao Paulo, Brazil
    
    [Rua Jaceru, 225 - Vila Gertrudes, São Paulo, Brazil, 04705-000](https://goo.gl/maps/Ln37ZizNgyku2vgJA)

* Florianópolis, Brazil
    
    [Rod. Admar Gonzaga, 440 Itacorubi - Florianópolis / SC 88034-000 - Brasil](https://goo.gl/maps/X9Z1MNwFPNfaYkPB9)

* Chile
    
    [Av Vitacura 2736,Las Condes, Región Metropolitana, Chile Floor 4](https://maps.app.goo.gl/gdWs3reDEp1W1yT86)

* Prague, Czech Republic

* Paris, France

* Munich, Germany
    
    [SimilarWeb, Office 01-111, C/O WeWork, Neuturmstrasse 5, BY, 80331 Munich](https://www.google.com/maps/place/WeWork+-+Altstadt-Lehel+-+Private+Broflchen+und+Coworking/@48.1381045,11.5809333,15z/data=!4m6!3m5!1s0x479e756d836d0329:0x57c2b4f7a0fe9290!8m2!3d48.1381045!4d11.5809333!16sg11f62wjwgn)

* Tokyo, JP
    
    [Otemachi Building 2F, 1-6-1 Otemachi, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo, 100-0004](https://goo.gl/maps/nJEUW65nmMn3YiXBA)

* Singapore
    
    [Asia Square Tower 2, 12 Marina View, #11-01, Singapore 018961](https://maps.app.goo.gl/ApPArjL7yfhvfdw98)

* London, UK

English

* Manage Cookies

© Similarweb LTD 2024 All Rights Reserved
